(Space Rice Cake)
(After a long, hard struggle with rice cakes, )
(the place grew into a decent restaurant.)
(And they finally opened the restaurant.)
(But the streets were empty.)
(She's posing for photos here.)
(But we're taking a break right now.)
(We're not taking a break. We're open for business!)
(With the labour-management conflict escalating, )
(the owner backed down and chose the carrot over the stick.)
(They joined forces again, )
(and Space Rice Cake has no empty tables left now.)
(Meanwhile, some people are approaching the restaurant.)
- Oh, my. Hello.
- Hello.
Welcome.
- How many in your party?
- Two.
- Two?
- Hello.
Welcome to our restaurant. But I'm sorry.
- We're currently...
- Yes?
- completely full.
- I see.
May I put you on the waitlist using this application?
- Sure.
- Okay. Got it.
Thank you so much.
- If you could wait just a bit, - Yes.
We'll contact you as soon as your table is ready.
We have people on the waitlist.
Do we?
- We have one party on the list.
- I see.
I'm not really used to being this famous.
What is going on?
This is way beyond our expectations.
- Yu Jin, did you tell them?
- Yes, I did.
- We have customers on the waitlist.
- Customers on the waitlist.
- The first party on our waitlist.
- Thank you. I owe it to you.
- You're welcome.
- Honesty, humility.
- Humility.
- Ahk.
(Screaming)
- Chef Kim Mi Hyun.
- Yes?
- Are you tired?
- I'm crazy.
- That's not what she asked.
- Sorry?
- She asked if you were tired.
- I asked if you were tired.
I'm crazy.
- How's everything going now?
- It's going well.
Is it?
- Have you closed out any tables?
- No, I haven't.
Can you check...
how the customers like original tteokbokki?
- How's everything going out there?
- They all love it.
- Is everything going well?
- Yes.
Do our customers seem happy with our food?
- Of course.
- Absolutely.
- Are they enjoying the food?
- Yes.
What did they say?
(Chef Young Ji, the anxious type)
Young Ji, they all really like your food.
- Really? Do they like it?
- Yes.
- You mean, original tteokbokki?
- Everything.
- Really? Thank you.
- Yes.
They all love your tteokbokki.
Really? I'm relieved.
Eun Ji has worked...
- all kinds of jobs.
- That's right.
She's a perfect and sexy career woman.
Thank you, Village Chief. I can tell...
you really got the word out.
We have some customers waiting outside.
- Really?
- Yes.
They're on our waitlist.
Thank you.
Thank you, everyone.
- Yes, ma'am.
- I'm your first customer.
- That's right, ma'am.
- I wish you great success.
Thank you, ma'am.
- I really enjoyed the food.
- Thank you.
- May you all be blessed.
- You too. Get home safely.
(The head of the women's association is getting ready to leave.)
Take your time and enjoy the food. We're off now.
Won't you take him with you?
Don't you have somewhere to be, Reverend?
- How much do I owe you?
- It's 12 dollars.
- Twelve dollars?
- Yes.
(Maybe he's sad to leave, so he chugs his slushy.)
- Are you leaving, sir?
- Yes.
Thank you for coming.
- Thank you.
- Get home safely.
Hello. I'm calling from Space Rice Cake.
(Eun Ji calls the waiting customer right away.)
Yes, you can come now.
(Meanwhile, Young Ji goes to check on the hall for the first time.)
Are you enjoying the food?
(Thumbs up)
- Thank you.
- It's good.
Is tteokramisu a big portion?
- No, the portion size isn't so big.
- Is it big enough for us to share?
I think it's big enough for you to share.
- It's delicious.
- Can we get pomegranate slushy too?
- Sure. Of course.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Tteokramisu cake.
(Thrilled to receive the very first dessert order)
Tteokramisu and pomegranate slushy.
(She starts making the dessert right away.)
(She cuts the coffee-soaked baekseolgi into smaller pieces.)
(In a pretty dessert cup, )
(she places the first layer.)
(The next step is...)
(to pipe the chestnut cream.)
(Here comes the key ingredient she learned to make.)
(Sticky)
(On top of the chestnut cream, )
(she puts real chestnuts to add some texture.)
(She adds another layer of baekseolgi.)
(She pipes the chestnut cream one more time.)
(She adds more real chestnuts.)
(Lastly, )
(she grates some chestnuts to make chestnut powder!)
(A big pile of chestnut powder)
(She decorates it with an apple mint leaf...)
(and a whole chestnut to wrap up.)
You did a wonderful job.
(The first tteokramisu chestnut is ready.)
- You really did a great job today.
- They're going to love it.
(He slices smoothly through the soft tteokramisu.)
(And he takes a big bite.)
It's good.
(The village chief takes a bite too.)
- It's sweet and delicious, right?
- It's good.
(The tteokramisu chestnut is completely devoured.)
- Is it good?
- Yes. The food is good here.
The chef here is very famous.
- It's true.
- Who's this chef, Uncle?
Her name is Lee Young Suk, I think.
(Laughing)
Her name is Lee Young Ji.
(Lee Young Suk, a famous chef in Goheung)
By the way, Yu Jin.
The dining room truly feels like a cosy parlour...
- Yes, indeed.
- with all the seniors there.
- It has a warm vibe.
- Yes.
- Order's up.
- Okay.
Small original tteokbokki,
tteokramisu chestnut, and fancy coffee slushy.
I'll do the dishes.
(With no orders for her coming in, Mimi steps up to do the dishes.)
(Young Ji starts making the small original tteokbokki.)
(The village chief, who contributed so much to the successful opening, )
(and his party are getting ready to leave.)
- I can ring you up here.
- Can you get their bill?
You had a small portion of original tteokbokki...
And pomegranate slushy too.
Your total comes to 45.9 dollars.
- Are you paying with a card...
- The table...
We'll pay for table three too.
Shall I ring you up for table three too?
Please give me a second.
(She rushes to find Mi Suk's bill.)
(But she can't tell which is hers.)
(She steps out with both for now.)
You had a small portion of original tteokbokki...
and tteokramisu chestnut.
Is that right?
- Actually...
- We had pollack roe pasta too.
That must be the bill for that table.
(She got it confused with another table.)
Right? I'm sorry.
- Then...
- How will you survive in business?
I know, right? What do I do?
(The village chief's table, total: 45.9 dollars)
(Mi Suk's table, total: 36.9 dollars)
(Total: 82.8 dollars)
(That's the total amount, but...)
Your total comes to 72.8 dollars.
I'm sorry about that.
(She has no idea she made a mistake at the register.)
Thank you.
We really enjoyed the food.
- Thank you.
- Go home safely. Thank you.
(Sighing with relief)
So this one was it. It was here.
(She stares suspiciously at the bill.)
(But she never realised she made a mistake.)
One small original tteokbokki is up.
Got it.
Let's do this!
All right.
(1 small original tteokbokki, 1 tteokramisu, 1 coffee slushy)
One small original tteokbokki is up.
(She serves the food quickly.)
You see, our plates are very heavy.
(Dirty plates keep rolling in without a break.)
- Thank you, Mimi.
- Don't worry about it.
Thank you so much.
Mimi, let me take over the dishes now.
No, that's okay. Hold on.
Go take a shower. Wait, no. That's not what I meant to say.
Am I...
Am I dirty?
(While Mimi is starting to lose her focus...)
- The pasta is good, isn't it?
- Yes, it's tasty.
Right. Everything is good.
Is the entire cast of "Earth Entertainment TV" here?
The whole cast of "Earth Entertainment TV" is here.
- Are all of you here?
- I understood her instantly.
All four of us from "Earth Entertainment TV" are here.
But I don't see Mimi.
Mimi is the one who made that pollack roe and clam pasta.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
Mimi made it.
(She delivers the news right away.)
Mimi, they're really enjoying your pollack roe and clam pasta.
- Really? I'm relieved.
- Yes.
And a customer asked for you. "Where is Mimi?"
- Young Ji.
- Pardon?
- I'll go to see this customer.
- Yes, Mimi? Okay.
- Hurry up. She just left.
- Okay.
(Rushing over to say hello)
Hello.
- You're still here. Hello.
- We'll come back.
- Did you enjoy the food?
- I'm a fan of yours.
Oh, really?
(Grateful)
I said my favourite was the pollack roe and clam pasta,
and she said you made it.
(She chuckles while saying, "She said you made it.")
Thank you.
Take care. I'll go back inside.
- Goodbye.
- Goodbye. Go home safely.
(The mini fan event is over.)
(Current Time: 3:30pm)
(10 hours have passed since they came to work.)
(That means it's about time their bodies started aching.)
Give me a second.
(Both the experienced member...)
(and the younger member are getting tired.)
(The sparkle in Yu Jin's eyes has vanished.)
(Mimi's joints are stiff.)
(Everyone is getting tired.)
(Even so, Young Ji gets it together and washes the dishes.)
- A thought just crossed my mind.
- What is it?
Do you think we're paying for our karma right now?
I'm having a great time.
I'm having a great time too.
(Customers rush in again.)
- Hello.
(The service team gets busy again.)
Please take a look and feel free to sit wherever you like.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
- Would you like a bigger table?
- That'd be nice.
All right. I'll get the bigger table ready for you.
(Switching to a 4-seater)
(Shouting gibberish)
I'm bringing in a table. Be careful.
- Princes.
- Hey, move aside.
I just called them "princes."
Then she said, "Hey, move aside."
- Thank you.
- I'll take it out. I'm sorry.
(They finished switching tables.)
Will that be these two dishes, then?
Got it. Let me know if you need anything else.
- And tteokramisu chestnut, please.
- Tteokramisu chestnut.
- We've got a new order in.
- That's great news.
For table 1, 1 original tteokbokki...
and one pollack roe and clam pasta.
A new order for one original tteokbokki.
- A medium size.
- Got it.
- So two medium original tteokbokki?
- It's a new order.
It's a new order from a new table.
- Got it.
- It's a new order.
- Thanks. Cheer up. We've got this!
- We've got this!
Here goes the rice cake.
(She puts garaetteok in for the first order.)
(Mimi checks the temperature of the deep fryer.)
Perfect timing.
- Two mediums, right?
- Yes.
(In the kitchen, Mimi prepares deep-fried food.)
(In the hall, Eun Ji serves dongchimi.)
Goodness. I'm so tired.
(Sighing)
This gentleman here says the prices are very low.
This gentleman over here? Thank you so much.
- You can charge him more.
- Thank you for your compliment.
(At the same time, Mimi...)
(finished making the deep-fried food for the original tteokbokki.)
(1 pollack roe and clam pasta)
(She moves on to making pollack roe and clam pasta.)
(As she focuses on making the pasta, )
(she has to put in the second batch of deep-fried food.)
(She goes back and forth between the fryer and the stove.)
It's about time for us...
to serve the food.
- It'll be ready in three minutes.
- Okay.
We can serve pollack roe and clam pasta first.
(Chuckling)
(Me?)
This dish takes longer to prepare.
That's the problem.
Once it gets sweet and soft,
you need to, Director,
pour water in the frying pan.
(Mimi: "Pour water in the frying pan.")
We can pour in a little more water.
Add a little bit of chicken stock.
(What she's trying to say is that it takes quite a long time.)
How's everyone doing right now?
I'm fine.
I love you.
Yes.
(Chuckling)
(Giggling)
Please say you love me.
I love you. I love you so much.
- I love you.
I love you.
- Medium original tteokbokki is up.
- Got it.
How's our pace? We're still a bit slow, right?
- Today is our first day.
- This is fast enough.
- Really? Are we doing okay?
- You're doing well.
(1 medium original tteokbokki)
It's our first day, so...
My original tteokbokki is quite consistent now.
(It's boiled down to perfection.)
(She adds the fried seafood on top of the tteokbokki.)
Young Ji, you're picking up speed. Nice.
- I'm multitasking right now.
- That's great.
- I love you.
- You're picking up speed.
- Eun Ji, I love you.
- I love you too, Young Ji.
(1 medium original tteokbokki)
Yu Jin, let me take over the dishes now.
Okay. Then Young Ji, can you...
Can you put this aside... Is she gone?
(At the same time, Young Ji is...)
(Putting food in her mouth)
Is she gone?
- I'm here. I'm listening.
- Can you put this aside?
(While heading over to help Yu Jin...)
I already washed it.
(Young Ji eats more food.)
- Make some room for this, please.
- Got it.
- Young Ji.
- Yes?
Why did you eat the leftover tteokbokki?
To figure out why they left it.
- Really?
- Yes.
Why didn't they finish it? Was the sausage too salty?
Or was the rice cake...
They left quite a lot.
So I ate some, and I realised...
Honestly, it was good.
I'll reduce the portion size from now on.
(It seems like portion control is needed.)
Just enough to leave them wanting more.
(The pollack roe and clam pasta is ready too.)
(1 pollack roe and clam pasta)
The pasta...
- is up. Should I serve it?
- Okay.
- Want to try serving it? Go ahead.
- Eun Ji. Shall I?
(Mimi is serving the food this time.)
Who ordered pollack roe and clam pasta?
(They find her cute.)
- Here.
- Oh, I see.
- Mimi.
- Hello.
- Oh, thank you, sir.
(1 pollack roe and clam pasta)
I tried my best to make it delicious.
This is Kim Mimi.
Please mix the thing that's on top with that thing...
- Try eating it that way, please.
- Okay. Thank you.
I think she was trying to tell you...
to gently break up and spread the pollack roe.
(She basically provided simultaneous interpretation.)
How are our customers doing?
- Our customers are...
- Are they having a good time?
Yes, they're having a good time. Most of them are families.
Are they enjoying the food?
- Absolutely.
- Really?
Honestly, I felt too rushed to watch them eat.
(Don't worry. We have Eun Ji, the manager.)
- Is it not too spicy for you?
- No.
- No. It's okay.
- For the children as well?
Please let me know when you're ready for dessert.
- Okay.
- Can we have it now?
I'll bring it now.
They're ready for the tteokramisu now.
(It just came out of the fridge?)
(We'll show you how that happened.)
(As soon as they received the order...)
I'll just make it now.
(Being smart, she made the dessert ahead of time.)
(Once the tteokramisu chestnut was ready, )
(she put it in the fridge.)
- I'll do the dishes for a bit.
- Okay.
(She did all of that and even helped with the dishes.)
Do you know Chef Kwon Sung Jun from "Culinary Class Wars?"
- That's his photo over there. Yes.
- Right.
- He's called Neapolitan Matfia.
- I watched the show.
We learned his recipe.
It's a reimagined version of tiramisu.
- Oh, my. It's good.
- It's good.
(Meanwhile, the kitchen is cleared of orders.)
I love you.
- Don't you love me?
- I love you.
If you love me, you must say it back to me.
I love you.
Not yet.
(Dirty plates are coming in instead of love.)
(Dirty plates)
Welcome.
They keep rolling in, right?
- Pass the baton to someone else.
- Okay.
(Even after that, dirty plates keep coming in.)
Coming through.
- What is it?
- Sorry?
- What were you doing?
- Nothing.
(Young Ji's soul is leaving her body.)
How are you all doing? Are you good? I love you.
I love you.
(Suddenly, the kitchen is filled with love.)
We must love even when we're dying of exhaustion.
(Seriously...)
You're right.
We must love. We must stick together even when we hate each other.
It's scary how Young Ji has so many different personas.
Sometimes she's like Ms. Ma Bok Rim, the tteokbokki legend.
She's just herself at other times.
- I love you.
- She turns into the head chef too.
(The dishes are done.)
(She walks over to Mimi, clutching her aching joints.)
(Groaning)
(As her back finally stretches, )
(her groans echo through the kitchen.)
Can you do it for me?
One, two, three.
(Groaning)
It's beautiful.
(Mimi bounces her knees with Young Ji on her back.)
(Her loud groans echo down the hallway and beyond.)
(Groaning and laughing)
- That's Young Ji's voice.
- Is it?
- She has a loud voice.
- It's okay.
- She's the loudest on the show.
- Yes, she's loud.
Her voice is so loud. It sounded like a street fight from afar.
She's always loud and boisterous. That's why she's called "Loud One."
(She helps Yu Jin stretch her back as well.)
- Okay. You feel better now, right?
- Yes.
- You feel better now, right?
Can you keep checking on the dining area?
- I'll take a look.
- They might be ready to pay.
(Young Ji springs into action.)
Hello, I'm the chef.
Are you enjoying the food?
- I recognise your voice.
- Hello.
Please enjoy your food and have a wonderful time.
Thank you. Sir, you're very handsome.
- Thank you.
- Please enjoy your food.
Hello. Did you just arrive?
You just arrived? Would you like to come in?
Yu Jin, we have customers.
- Hello.
- Yu Jin, we have customers.
Hello, baby. A baby is here. It's a baby.
- A baby is here.
- Hi.
Please sit wherever you'd like.
- Hyun Seok.
- Gosh, aunt.
- Hello, uncle.
What brings you here? Hello.
What do you mean? We came to eat.
We happened to see this place while passing by.
- Hello.
- Our baby.
- Long time, no see.
(Young Ji gets a baby chair ready first.)
(Passing it to the expert)
- Do you need a baby chair?
- Yes.
Thank you.
I'll help you with the payment.
(She helps with the payment after handing over the chair.)
- Thank you. Please take care.
- Thank you.
Shall we try this one?
- Or that one?
- Won't it be too spicy?
Wait, which one is better?
- Let's try that one.
- Get a small one.
Hi there.
- Come here.
- A small one.
Come to grandma. Come to me.
- He's still shy around strangers.
- I can see that.
- Another order came in.
- Okay.
One small original tteokbokki...
and one chestnut tiramisu.
- What?
- One chestnut tiramisu.
- Chestnut tiramisu?
- Wait.
I should be upset that I didn't get an order.
But I’m just so happy that I get to support Young Ji.
I can focus on supporting her.
(Starting the tteokbokki with some support)
(While waiting for it to cook down, )
(let's watch something cute.)
- That's what happened.
- I see.
Come. Come to grandma.
- You can come to me now.
- You can do it.
I guess he's not ready yet.
Let's get going.
- You should pay.
- Okay, I'll go and pay.
This and...
there’s an order from the table next to us.
- Yes.
- Please add that to the bill.
Okay.
With the order from the table next to you,
it's 43.9 dollars in total.
- Would you like to pay in cash?
- Yes.
Here's your 6.1 dollars.
- Thank you.
- You're carrying the cash register.
- Have a good day.
- Thank you.
The tteokbokki will be ready in two minutes.
(Just then...)
(Crying)
- The baby is crying.
- Why is he crying?
Eun Ji, go and check on him.
- Is it because I'm taking too long?
- No.
(Is the baby crying?)
- Hello.
(Doctor Finger, Doctor Finger)
(Where are you?)
(A sudden sing-along session begins.)
(A 34-year-old floor manager doing her best)
(And a 1-year-old customer who cannot stop her)
Give her a smile.
I'm hiding.
Peekaboo.
(Not sure what to think)
I'm hiding. Peekaboo!
Could you move a little when I say peekaboo?
Okay.
I'm hiding.
Peekaboo!
(A faint smile slowly appears.)
I think you moved a little too much.
(The dining area has quieted down.)
Eun Ji is the best.
(The medium original tteokbokki is ready.)
This tteokbokki is delicious. I made it.
Gosh, thank you.
- Eun Ji.
- Yes?
Excuse me. It's my first time serving.
Eun Ji, do I put this on top of that?
Yes, I'll help you.
Please enjoy it.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
We made the rice cakes ourselves today.
- You made them?
- Yes, from start to finish.
Enjoy your food and stay healthy.
Baby, don't cry anymore.
(Chef Young Ji has completely given it her all.)
(It may be broad daylight, but she’s been working for 11 hours.)
(But it's not over yet.)
(Overtime to-do list: Cleaning the dining area, washing dishes, )
(refrigerating the leftover rice cakes, reviewing today's service, )
(checking inventory, staff meal, prepping the sauce...)
(And she has to be back at work bright and early tomorrow.)
We'll take our last order at 4:44pm.
- At 4:44pm?
- Yes.
(Current Time: 4:37pm)
(Just then, a group of 3 young customers arrives.)
It'll be delicious.
It'll be our last order. They're the last customers.
- Hello.
- Welcome to Space Rice Cake.
By the way, could you explain...
what ghost pepper tteokbokki is?
Don't Eat Ghost Pepper Tteokbokki, It's a Challenge!
(Ghost pepper tteokbokki)
(As the eldest gives it all until the end)
I feel like I'm about to cry.
I feel so sorry for her.
They say when you really love someone, you start to feel...
this deep compassion for each other.
That's why I feel sorry for her sometimes.
Not just sometimes. It happened ten times yesterday.
(Finally realising how Young Ji really feels)
See that? Do you feel the same way?
We're sisters after all.
Our Jade Emperor Tteokbokki is...
made with ghost peppers.
They're the spiciest peppers in the world,
and it's an eating challenge.
- My gosh.
- Also known as...
They'll be your last customers, so please do your best.
- Okay.
- We always do our best.
Whether it's the last customer, the first customer,
a customer in the middle of the day, or the seventh customer,
you give it your all. That's the mindset of running your business.
Just because they’re the last customer doesn’t mean...
- Think of it...
- What kind of mindset is that?
- as mala-style tteokbokki.
- The 3rd, 4th, 5th, 6th, 7th...
- Please excuse me for a minute.
- Sure.
Chef, can you be quiet?
(A voice that sounds like a serious scolding)
We can hear you very clearly.
You're embarrassing us.
How amateur must we look...
to the customers outside?
Please, Chef.
She's really getting chewed out.
We can hear the chef yelling all the way over here.
He told us to work hard for the last customers, so I...
- You'd better work hard.
- I mean...
Do you know why?
- They took on the challenge.
- Okay.
Did you warn them that it was incredibly spicy?
It's so spicy that it burns your butt hole.
As the person in charge of the challenge,
- why don't you go over there?
- Okay.
(The challenge authority has arrived.)
Hello again.
The head chef is here to officially announce the challenge.
Hello.
Did you order the challenge?
- How spicy is it?
- You haven't ordered it yet?
- It'll tear your butt hole.
Try not to scare them away.
It's a little spicier than Yeopgi Tteokbokki Original.
Then we can do it.
- But...
- I only eat the spicy type.
It's not just spicy. The portion is huge.
I'm 175cm tall.
- Then I'll only eat what's spicy.
- Can we get a smaller size?
No, you can't.
(One size)
(It's free if you finish it in 20 minutes.)
The three of you can take on the challenge.
- Yes.
- Then we'll take on the challenge.
- You take on the challenge?
- This is amazing.
(It's finally Jade Emperor Tteokbokki.)
(Dead serious)
- Thank you.
- Okay, nice.
(The reason why the head chef is this nervous)
- It’s like they’re challenging me.
- That's right.
I made it as spicy as I can possibly handle.
"Here, try this."
- I'm saying that to everyone.
- I like that idea.
(As a result...)
(After countless rounds of practice, )
(she finally reached the spicy level.)
This is ghost pepper tteokbokki.
The length is 175cm.
It's spicy,
and it's impossible to handle.
This is nothing other than Lee Young Ji.
I think of it as myself.
(First, she checks the 175cm-long whole garaetteok.)
I'll give them the prettiest one of the bunch today.
This is the prettiest one.
(It fills the pan.)
It's time to show what you've got.
I'm seriously going to show them.
I won't go easy on them today.
Defeat Lee Young Ji.
Finish the whole thing and it’s free.
I feel alive when I make this.
Making this makes me really happy.
(It's another spicy sauce.)
(Here comes chilli bean sauce.)
This is the last one.
(A generous amount of chilli bean sauce)
I can do this.
(And now, some numbing Sichuan pepper oil)
I'm adding capsaicin too.
One, two.
(And Young Ji gives a mysterious smile.)
One teaspoon of ghost pepper.
Directors, cover your nose.
- Hold your breath.
I walked past it for a second, and... Goodness.
Hold your breath!
There's ghost pepper ahead.
I'm adding 175cm-long rice cakes.
Gosh, the smell is insane.
- I'll start frying.
- Please go ahead.
(While the toppings are frying to perfection)
Here are your drinks.
If you look closely, there are a lot of cute little details.
We’re the first place...
to combine a traditional rice mill...
We combined a traditional rice mill...
with a tteokbokki place.
It's like a fine dining omakase experience.
That's right.
- Chef Eun Ji.
- Yes?
Tell everyone waiting for the challenge...
that today’s version is especially spicy.
- It's especially spicy today?
- Exactly.
(A practice run)
- Your Jade Emperor Tteokbokki...
- Yes.
Challenge is ready.
- Exactly like that.
- It’s so spicy that...
if things go wrong,
you might...
(Let's stop there.)
(Adding sliced beef loin as a topping)
(The beef loin is perfectly cooked.)
One minute before the dish is ready.
(She tastes it for one last time.)
It's extreme today.
Today's first challenge.
(Young Ji's first challenge dish)
(It's finally ready.)
Chef, please serve the challenge dish yourself.
Okay.
(She carries Jade Emperor Tteokbokki with solemn determination.)
The person who made it is here herself.
- Be careful.
- This is unbelievable.
- Be careful, everyone.
- Hello.
This is especially spicy today.
I take no responsibility for anything...
that happens from now on.
(The challenge starts.)
- Twenty minutes?
- I don't think we can finish it.
(The time limit of 20 minutes starts.)
Wait.
(Starting with the most confident customer)
(Humming)
(She seems surprisingly calm.)
- Is the spiciness okay?
- It's okay.
It's just...
deliciously spicy.
Isn't the spiciness okay?
It's okay because the rice cakes are thick.
It's less spicy than I expected.
Young Ji.
I hear that they're enjoying the tteokbokki.
That's the best news I've heard all day.
(She's clearly upset.)
- What about her?
- Tell her to join us.
- Right.
- Hey.
Hurry over. You're a spice addict.
- Is it spicy?
- No, it's not.
It's not spicy at all.
A new side plate.
- Hello.
- Thank you.
You invited someone else. You should've told me.
Thank you so much.
Please relax and enjoy yourselves.
(An unexpectedly fun challenge in progress)
They seemed to be enjoying the challenge very much.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
Here's the whole point of a challenge item.
It keeps getting spicier...
because people actually succeeded at eating it the first time.
Every time someone succeeds, it gets even spicier.
Due to the people who succeed,
others get annoyed, and their pride gets hurt.
That's what makes it a challenge dish.
- You'd better eat more.
- You too.
(They each take a bite happily.)
(Success)
- Did you succeed?
- Yes.
Congratulations.
(Gasping)
You're the first ones to clear the challenge.
- Did you really succeed?
- Congratulations.
- Congratulations - Hey, hey.
Congratulations on finishing the whole thing.
(The song is cheerful, but the head chef is burning inside.)
- The five...
- Wasn't it spicy?
- Wasn't it very spicy?
- It wasn't spicy.
- It wasn't spicy? No way.
Could you lift up the plate?
- We'll take a photo of you all.
- Really?
- I'll do it with a Polaroid camera.
- Here's the Polaroid camera.
(Challenge Prize 1, taking a photo with a Polaroid camera)
I'll take a photo.
- One, two, three.
- I can't believe they finished it.
Click.
This is for those who clear the challenge.
Congratulations again.
Thank you.
Thanks to you, it will be spicier...
for those who take on this challenge tomorrow.
It will be much spicier.
Your total is only 29.9 dollars.
(Jade Emperor Tteokbokki is free when you succeed.)
- Aren't you glad that you did it?
- Yes.
We succeeded because it was delicious.
Really? I'll tell everyone in the kitchen.
- Thank you.
- Please come again.
- Goodbye.
I have plans to make it spicier.
I just went easy on them.
(It's time to close the restaurant.)
(Open for business)
(Closed for business)
- Let's clean up.
- Yes, let's clean up.
(Current Time: 5:52pm)
Gosh, Young Ji should come and look at this.
Young Ji.
- Young Ji, Mimi.
- Yes?
- It's a very beautiful sight.
- It really is.
- Mimi should come too.
- Hey, Mimi.
This is why...
- Young Ji.
- I'm about to cry.
Girls.
- Take a look.
- It's going to make me cry.
They finished all the food.
- So...
- It's really going to make me cry.
This is their response to your cooking.
- It looks delicious.
- They even finished the dongchimi.
This is their response.
- They must've enjoyed it.
- It was very well received.
We couldn't go over it because we were too busy.
You're right.
- This is incredible.
- Eun Ji,
you worked so hard today.
- Well done, everyone.
- Thank you.
Let's give ourselves a round of applause for our hard work.
(Patting herself on the back)
- First of all, our two servers...
- Yes.
You two served customers, washed dishes,
made chestnut tiramisu, made slushies,
and even attracted customers in the beginning.
Don't forget the dongchimi.
- Dongchimi.
- You also made dongchimi.
You filmed Reels, became balloon decorations for the event.
You did a bit of everything, helped us out, supported us,
- and took care of us. And...
- We went grocery shopping.
You even went grocery shopping...
in the pouring rain.
You fought through the typhoon and washed dishes.
You managed to keep your composure and your spirits up.
Give yourselves a big round of applause...
for your fair play.
- I really like working with her.
- Next is Kim Mi Hyun.
- She's very smart.
- You washed dishes,
rinsed dishcloths, cut the rice cakes,
made jeolpyeon, became my friend...
and my right-hand woman. You washed dishes,
made pollack roe and clam pasta.
Everyone loves your pollack roe and clam pasta.
Everyone likes your food.
You also made fried food, took it out,
let it dry, cooled it down, and plated it.
You kept me sane,
you set the timer and made sure the timer went off.
- She's perfect.
- Please clap for Mi Hyun.
(It was my pleasure.)
- Well done today.
- You worked the hardest.
Give yourself a compliment too.
- Give yourself a compliment.
- Right.
You made the sauce, prepped ingredients,
- grilled, and did everything.
- You created the challenge.
You came up with the challenge...
and planned everything.
- You're cute.
- You washed dishes,
- assigned everyone their roles, - Right.
And got the aprons ready.
Anyway, well done. I'm glad that we have pockets on our aprons.
- Was it uncomfortable?
- No, it's comfortable.
- I really like it.
- Let me know if there's a problem.
- It's the best.
- So today,
- how did we do on sales?
- Today's sales?
(Day 1 of business)
(The sales are revealed.)
Get ready.
- Seriously.
- I will announce...
- the sales amount.
- How much did we make?
Let's start with the card reader.
- We earned 296.8 dollars.
- It's about 300 dollars.
When rounded up, it's 300 dollars.
(Self-congratulatory applause)
- That's only from the card reader.
- How about cash?
How about cash?
Oh, my.
- We earned 300 dollars.
- The total is 400 dollars.
We earned close to 400 dollars.
It's about 390 dollars.
(4 small original tteokbokki, 6 medium original tteokbokki, )
(3 ghost pepper mala tteokbokki, 1 Jade Emperor Tteokbokki...)
(Minus 11.5 dollars due to Yu Jin's mistake)
(Total sales: 327.8 dollars)
- We earned a lot.
- How did we make so much?
Let's clap for each other.
It's a big success today.
- Seriously...
- Let's hug each other.
- Hug me.
- We'll be busier tomorrow.
When I say "honesty," please say "humility."
- Honesty.
- Humility.
- Ahk.
You guys are the best.
Let's wrap things up and buy some at the supermarket.
- I'd be so grateful.
- Buy it at the supermarket.
Anything sounds good.
Let's grill it here...
and enjoy it with tteokbokki.
- Enjoy your food.
- Thank you.
- Bon appetit.
- It's mostly uncooked,
- so take care of it yourself.
- Okay.
No problem.
Well done, everyone.
We bought some really good meat.
(Exclaiming)
The meat is excellent.
Help yourself.
Aren't you glad that we're eating meat?
Once we wash the rice, are we done for today?
- You guys can go home first.
- Unbelievable.
We still have to make basil pesto.
- We have to try it.
- You're right.
We need to taste it.
(Next is tasting the new basil tteokbokki.)
I'm telling you, we're amazing.
We prep, we run the restaurant,
and we do more research after closing.
We even make our own rice cakes.
We're seriously amazing.
What worries me is that basil is tricky.
Once people get a taste of it, all of them want it.
Young Ji isn't very experienced with making basil dishes.
- It's not something...
- You never tried it at home.
- you can practice with at home.
- Right.
You've definitely been showing your INFP side more lately.
- Really?
- I used to question it.
"Is she really an INFP?"
- But lately...
- In what way?
The way you've been feeling overwhelmed lately.
Or is it because of the situation?
Right.
Or maybe I'm starting to understand what you're thinking.
- Maybe you were like this before.
- That's possible.
You never used to show it, but now you're letting it show.
You mean, how I worry about things?
- Your worries...
- Yes.
- and your tender heart.
- My tender heart?
Should you tell me that you love me or not?
I shouldn't.
I say I love you when I do.
- But I don't love you now.
- Do you say it when you love me?
Of course. I'm very sincere about it.
That's even funnier.
There was a moment of absolute rage...
when she was making an ex-boyfriend toast.
"It's my first time running a business too!"
- She said that earlier.
- It's how Young Ji looked.
- When?
- When you were cutting jeolpyeon.
- Mimi looked...
- Was she being serious?
Like a psychopath when she was just slicing the jeolpyeon.
Can I honestly give my one-line review of Mimi?
She's an independence activist.
(It means that she's that strong and unshakable.)
- That's what I think.
- This is all we could hear.
- We didn't even have customers.
- Exactly.
(Walking the long road of jeolpyeon single-handedly)
All of us are...
- unusual.
- Shall I make basil tteokbokki?
What?
- I didn't hear you.
- I'll go and make it.
- We'll go with you.
- Hold on, Young Ji.
- I mean...
- Let's do it together.
It's because...
(It's time for basil.)
- Where's the strainer?
- It's on top of this.
Eun Ji, did you measure 15kg?
I'll make three at the same time.
(The kitchen team tests the new dish.)
I'll start.
The whole black pepper was there, wasn't it?
(The happy break is too short.)
Do you want to go over there?
There isn't enough space here.
(But the working hours are long.)
I guess the balance is off.
(Two hands that never get a chance to rest)
One, two, three.
(It gets heavier by the day.)
(They finish soaking the rice again today.)
It's done.
- An Yu Genius.
- Yes?
Please chop a lot of green onions today.
I was going to do that tomorrow.
- I'll chop a lot tomorrow.
- I'm sorry.
(Laughing)
You want me to chop them?
(Stop)
- This is the basil sauce?
- Yes.
We still don't have a ladle yet.
I'm a bit nervous. It's my first time trying it.
(Tomorrow's new dish has Eun Ji feeling nervous.)
Broccolino Basiliano.
This looks delicious.
(She pulls out a huge storage container.)
I can tell by looking at the sauce. What do we do?
Can we try some?
Here I go.
Six cups.
Nine cloves of garlic.
Pine nuts.
One more cup of Parmigiano Reggiano cheese.
(Young Ji made it earlier.)
That's great.
Eun Ji, I'll start cooking it.
This feels promising.
Nice.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
Gosh, it smells insanely good.
- This is delicious.
- Try to find...
- which side feels easier for you.
- This is very good.
I'll decorate the dish.
Yes, start with the broccoli.
(Fried broccoli)
(Tater tots)
(Sun-dried tomatoes)
Isn't it pretty?
I should buy one of these too.
The colours...
Basil tteokbokki is ready.
- It's my first time trying it.
- Me too.
I'd appreciate it if you could give me...
- your honest opinion.
- It's really my first time.
Thank you for the food.
Make sure to try some fried broccoli too.
(Suddenly tense)
(Nodding)
(Humming in approval)
- I like it.
- I'm glad to hear that.
It'd be perfect with the original tteokbokki.
- We can alternate between the two.
- That'd be amazing.
I have a suggestion.
I won't be here tomorrow,
but what do you think about adding bacon here?
That's a cheat code, but...
If it's too much extra work, there's no need.
Basil tteokbokki is already the most labour-intensive one to make.
Don't you normally make it with sausage?
- I forgot about the sausage.
- There's sausage in it.
- In that case...
- There's sausage.
- There's sausage in it.
- I'll add sausage to it.
I have another opinion.
- It's good.
- I can't eat a lot of greasy food.
- Right.
- I know.
Should we try sprinkling some black pepper on it?
- Let's try that.
- Black pepper?
I said that it had a strong creamy flavour.
This has less basil flavour than the original.
I'll add a little more of that tomorrow.
- If you fix that, it'd be perfect.
- Do you want to practice it now?
Sure.
- No, I wasn't serious.
- What?
(That's enough now.)
- We have to go home together, - Shall I do it now?
- No.
- don't we?
(Current Time: 10:40pm)
- Honesty.
- Humility.
- Ahk.
- Ahk. I love you.
Let's go.
- Take everything with you.
- Let's go.
Get some rest. Sleep well.
(After a long, exhausting day)
Have a good night.
(It's time to get some rest.)
I can't help worrying about the restaurant.
Here's what I'm worried about.
- Did you lock the door properly?
- I did.
What if someone breaks in...
- and steals the basil pesto?
- I know.
If they steal our dongchimi, they're done for.
- Did someone break in?
- Hold on.
You got an alert.
"A door opening has been detected. Check the recorded footage?"
- Hey.
- My goodness.
(The footage is sent to Earth Arcaders in real time.)
- Who is it?
- But I locked the door.
(The silhouette looks very familiar.)
- It's live footage.
- Is it Director Yeong Seok?
- What?
- Isn't it Yeong Seok?
It's his bucket hat.
With that unmistakable middle-aged man vibe,
it's definitely Yeong Seok.
What's amazing is that it's nighttime,
- Right.
- but you can see it clearly.
- There's no glare or anything.
- You're right.
I went into the app earlier and turned on security mode.
(Simply set it up after closing for the day)
As soon as movement was detected, I got an alert.
- It's reassuring.
- What is it called?
- Let's get some rest.
- Let's go to bed.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- We'll hassle Yeong Seok tomorrow.
- Good job, everyone.
- See you tomorrow.
(Young Ji and Yu Jin's room)
Yu Jin, how was business today?
Today? I thought...
(The head chef wants to know how her employee feels.)
When I first met the elderly customers, it was a little hard.
To interact with them?
I struggled with how to keep things flowing naturally.
Meeting elderly customers was...
a little challenging, but things got better after that.
Today was better than I expected.
It looked like you were having a hard time today.
- I thought I was going to lose it.
- I know. You struggled a lot.
Was I being sensitive?
No, you just looked exhausted.
I could tell that you were overwhelmed.
Normally, I'm not...
- Calm?
- a meticulous person.
- I see.
- That's what makes it hard.
(And so, a moment of self-reflection began.)
I really hate seeing myself when I'm anxious.
(Young Ji's problem: Being an anxious head chef)
- I understand how you feel.
- Right?
Here's how...
I noticed that you were anxious.
- You asked 50 questions.
- I did?
"Should I stop it now? Should I take it out?"
"Can I take it out directly? Should I stop doing it?"
"Should I put this back in?"
You wanted to check everything...
- that you were doing.
- Right.
To know if it was right or wrong.
- I couldn't trust myself.
- Exactly.
Yu Jin, what's your biggest concern?
What I'm worried about is...
- calculating the bills.
- That must be so hard.
It's harder than you think.
My hands were shaking...
with customers waiting right in front of me.
Earlier today,
you and your jeolpyeon...
I thought that you were possessed...
by a spirit.
(The older girls are also talking about what happened.)
You weren't listening.
You didn't answer when we called you.
It was so scary.
(Mimi's problem: Her obsession over jeolpyeon)
You can't help but fixate on something.
Mimi, what time are we getting up tomorrow?
- At 6:30am.
- Why so early?
It's great to run a restaurant with you girls.
(Hopefully, things will go smoothly tomorrow.)
I agree.
(It's the morning of their 2nd day of business.)
(As if it never rained, )
(the sunshine is pouring down.)
(A bright, sunny morning brought the village back to life.)
(What will Space Rice Cake look like today?)
(Current Time: 6:20am)
(The first one to arrive at work is Mimi.)
Come out.
What's wrong with my voice?
Hello. What's that?
This is the headscarf Eun Ji bought for me.
(She looks like she's ready to join a hiking club.)
I was seriously in denial when I woke up this morning.
Is it 6am already?
Is it really 6am?
(Going back to work only about 7 hours later)
It's cold in the morning and evening here.
- I know.
- Will we get customers today?
- If it isn't cold like now...
- Right.
They'll like outdoors more.
- Hello.
Hello.
We make tteokbokki.
- Hello.
- Please come and try it.
- Where is it?
- We'll make tteokbokki there.
- It's called Space Rice Cake.
- In front of a raw fish restaurant.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- What are the two doing?
- They're coming.
- The kitchen team seems impatient.
- I know.
They're always...
- Could you go first?
- Okay.
(The impatient kitchen team gets the signboard out.)
Okay.
(On the 2nd day of business, they're ready to go.)
- Honesty. Ahk.
- Humility. Ahk.
Put on your apron.
- We can do it.
- Let's go.
I love you all.
- Shall we get started?
- Yes.
- Shall I put the strainer on top?
(Rice that they soaked yesterday)
We soaked 15kg yesterday. We should weigh it again though.
The thought of lifting it makes me nervous.
- One, two, three.
(Starting with hard physical work early in the morning)
(Grunting)
(A rice flour team drowning in cries of agony)
Are you all right?
We're okay.
- It's so heavy.
- The weight is...
It's 19kg.
- It absorbed a lot.
- It absorbed a lot of water.
(It bulked up by 4kg overnight from soaking up all that water.)
(Shouting)
(Thankfully, they get their morning strength workout.)
- Stay strong.
- You can do it.
It's really heavy.
(There's nothing easy about making rice cakes.)
Oh, my.
We can pull it off if we put our mind to it.
This is very heavy. It'll be over soon, Eun Ji.
What happened to the photo studio of us making rice cakes?
- I'll take photos of you.
- Okay.
- Looking as tired as possible...
- Get both of us in the frame.
- Like this... I'll stay low.
- Looking worn out...
- One, two, three.
- Should I look at the camera?
Make it look more gruelling.
- Without looking at the camera?
- What?
Face the camera...
but stay focused on work.
(A staged shot made with the photographer’s soul)
A look that says, "Our rice cakes are the best."
"It's delicious."
- Thank you.
- It's done.
(They're back to work after the photo shoot.)
My back is about to give out.
(Mixing away)
(They even brought in the latest technology, a blender.)
We're using some modern technology.
Is there any certification for making tteokbokki?
- Or making rice cakes.
- We can get certified now.
- All right!
- You're amazing.
Rice flour is an impressive thing.
(Rice flour is getting piled up.)
- Flour is everything.
- It turned out perfect.
(Once the finely ground rice flour is transferred into the steamer)
- Rice flour is ready.
- Way to go.
(Turning on the steamer at the right time)
Here it comes.
It takes some time. It'll be ready in 20 minutes.
It's hot, so be careful.
Making rice cakes is no easy job.
(When covered with a cloth, baekseolgi gets ready.)
Nice. You're doing so well.
Mimi, I assembled the rice cake shaper.
Young Ji, you know exactly what to do now.
- Mi Hyun, let's make rice cakes.
- Yes, let's go.
(After steaming it thoroughly)
- Are we starting with jeolpyeon?
- Yes.
(Putting baekseolgi into the rice cake shaper)
It smells so good today.
- The rice cakes look good today.
- I agree.
It smells good too.
(Nervous)
- Today's rice cakes are the best.
- Are they the best?
(Yu Jin also takes a bite.)
Gosh, Eun Ji.
It tastes like something you'd buy at a shop.
I'll pull it out,
- so could you put it in?
- I'll push it in.
- Here we go.
- Turn on the water...
and start.
(When Mimi puts in the baekseolgi)
Nice.
It's coming out really nicely.
Okay, it's the thicker one now.
- You got a rhythm going.
- That's good.
Young Ji, you really got the hang of it.
- How does it look?
- It's insanely pretty.
- This is insane.
- It's amazing today.
Oh, my.
Shouldn't we become professional rice cake chefs?
- The jeolpyeon is amazing today.
- It's what you buy at a shop.
It looks great.
The two of you got perfect teamwork.
- I'll pull out some garaetteok.
- We're done here.
(She starts on garaetteok with keeping the momentum.)
That's great.
That looks good.
It's coming out smoothly. The size is consistent.
(Soon, there's only silence in the kitchen.)
Easy does it. Keep your hands relaxed.
(The usually boisterous Young Ji is nowhere to be found.)
We're almost done.
(When it comes to making rice cakes, she's completely serious.)
Keep it smooth. Okay.
Like you're caressing it. Yes.
- Seeing her do it makes me tear up.
- Why?
This is touching. We're definitely filming a documentary.
- Yes, this is a documentary.
- It really is.
(Before long, everyone is sincere about making rice cakes.)
There's one thick part. Just make that thin.
- Let's look for it.
- Okay.
- I'll make it thinner overall.
- It looks okay now.
- It's great.
- It turned out well today.
- It's really amazing today.
(Perfectly smooth garaetteok is ready.)
- We're done. It's not bad...
- It's not bad.
Including the middle part.
(While the kitchen team is busy making rice cakes)
I don't have to chop the green onions diagonally, right?
- Chop them however you want.
- Okay.
As you like.
(In charge of green onions, in charge of chilli peppers)
(Scraping)
It sounds like someone is laughing.
(Inhaling loudly)
(They're a magical duet.)
(That's how she chops Cheongyang chilli pepper.)
(Chopping red chilli)
(The Vienna sausages are done in an instant.)
(Next is prepping tteokramisu chestnut.)
(When Eun Ji cuts the baekseolgi, )
(Yu Jin takes it over and soaks it in coffee.)
We can finish it in no time after soaking it in coffee.
Gosh. You work quickly, Yu Jin.
- Thank you.
- You're so fast.
(Lastly, after starting the slushy machine, )
(all prep is done.)
- Okay. The kitchen team.
- Yes.
Let me check.
You asked for another rice paddle yesterday.
- Yes.
- A silicone rice paddle.
And three more measuring spoons.
Three more.
What else did you mention, Young Ji?
What did I mention?
- Arm sleeves.
- Arm sleeves. Yes.
- She wanted long and warm ones.
- Yes.
And they can be in any pattern.
I want to feel intimidating when I wear them.
Was there anything else? I think they mentioned something.
Let's get going for now.
I'm excited.
This is my favourite time of the day.
I finished prepping fast for this.
(Celebrating performance)
(Off to the grocery store!)
Gosh. I can't wait.
I hope they have new items.
It's about that time.
(They've arrived in town.)
- How much did we spend yesterday?
- How much did we spend?
Will you tell us how much we spent yesterday?
We spent about 300 dollars, right?
(Splurge list)
(General store: 103 dollars, Grocery store: 36.57 dollars)
(Korean Beef: 39 dollars, Mart: 93.43 dollars, Chicken: 28)
(They spent 300 dollars.)
We made 100 dollars, then.
Eun Ji, hold on.
Let's limit our spending today.
We shouldn't hurt our sales.
That's right.
How about spending just 100 dollars today?
Hey, it's the general store.
My heart is racing.
- Hold on. Let's calm down.
- Calm down.
It'll be 100 dollars.
- We'll spend 100 dollars.
- Okay.
We'll spend only 50 dollars here.
Yu Jin.
- I think this is okay.
- That's cool.
Hey, Yu Jin.
Eun Ji.
This is why I love this place.
We only need to ladle once if it's that big.
- Gosh. Yu Jin.
- Twice tops.
Look, Yu Jin.
We can fit five ice cubes in it.
Yu Jin.
- Yes. It keeps the rain out too.
- It's as big as your face.
It can keep the rain out.
- Ma'am. Okay.
- Wait, Eun Ji.
Please hold on.
I think it will work better.
It's deeper.
- It's seven dollars. Is it okay?
- It's okay.
- I'll write it down.
- Yes. Seven dollars.
Ma'am, is there a measuring...
Is there a measuring spoon?
Yes, sure. That's it.
Gosh. Thank you.
- Now...
- We need three.
- We need 3.
- Then it's 9 dollars.
Okay.
It's getting tighter.
Today, we have our own...
- We're exercising self-control.
- Yes.
- Whenever we were here, - Once...
- we went crazy.
- Yes.
So we're trying moderation.
Yu Jin, look at this.
Hold on. Is it for the chestnut cream?
(She found another giant cooking tool.)
Wait, do you want to use it for the rice? The rice flour?
The rice flour.
This place is crazy.
Hey, Yu Jin. I want...
I want to live here.
Eun Ji, with that,
we can handle 30kg of rice flour.
(It's big enough to break rice clumps at once.)
We do need it.
You can't understand why we need it unless you tried it.
No. You have no idea.
You don't understand.
- And now...
- What do we have to buy?
We couldn't find the silicone rice paddle.
- Gosh, Yu Jin. Isn't this it?
- Was it a silicone one?
- Yu Jin.
- Hold on, Eun Ji.
- What did you say?
- I found it.
- Look. It's expensive.
- Gosh, Eun Ji.
Let's speed up.
- Let's speed up.
- Gosh, Eun Ji.
They have new teen-style hairbands.
- Goodness. Is it leopard print?
- Hairbands.
- Hold on.
- They have hairbands now.
I'd buy one if it were pink.
- What? It's pink.
- They have a pink one.
- What now?
- You are meant to buy it.
But it's...
(Surprised)
(How do I look?)
Hey, you have to wear it today.
- Let me take a look.
- Yu Jin.
You have to put it on today.
(I should buy it, right?)
Hey, you have to wear it today.
(Grocery list: A hairband)
What?
Eun Ji, what do you think about this apple print?
- Goodness.
I want these.
- Let's get one.
- They're so cute.
- I picked the ones for the lady.
- I wore them backwards.
I picked red ones or Ms. Lee Young Ji.
How do I look? Be honest.
(Ta-da)
Now, it's a bit...
Do I look bad?
- Are those better?
- You won't wear them today, though.
They're cute.
Aren't these cute?
Well, you won't wear them today.
I'm not going to buy them.
(She's deeply hurt.)
- I won't take them.
- To be honest,
they don't match your style today.
I won't take them.
These are for Young Ji. She'll like them.
They look intimidating.
We bought everything.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- As for milk, - Yes.
We need 3 cartons of 1,000ml each.
Can we just buy these?
- Yes, let's buy those big ones.
- Will they hate them?
- We'll buy the 2.3L ones.
- Yes.
- Should we get 2 of these?
- Yes, 2 big ones.
These kitchen hooks are cute.
(They're gone off track again.)
These are really cute, right?
- We can hang our ladles.
- Should we put it up?
Let's put them near the dessert station.
We can hang 7 items, and it can hold up to 2kg.
(They've decided to buy the hooks.)
We have to go for it, Yu Jin.
Let's go for it, Eun Ji.
We can't walk from here.
It's 10:08am. We have to leave at 10:30am.
Do you want gimbap?
- Yes.
- Then get this done by 10:20am.
- I... Okay.
- Let's hurry.
- Let's go.
- What do I need to do?
(They grab the milk.)
(Moving swiftly to get gimbap)
- I'm so happy to see you.
- Thank you.
Let's go, Yu Jin.
(Current Time: 10:25am)
I'll hold it.
We have to print the photos.
(They briefly forgot about the photos.)
Run, Eun Ji. We don't have time.
They told us to be back by 11am.
Hop in quickly.
Hop... Hop in quickly.
(Got it.)
(The photo studio is 3 minutes away by car.)
What? Gijeongtteok sounds tasty.
It must be hard for them too.
Whenever I see a rice cake place, I think about how hard it is.
Yes. It's a tough job.
(They arrived exhausted.)
- Good morning.
- Hello.
We need a total of 4 prints in A4 size.
- We'll send you two photos.
- Okay.
(Calling the kitchen team while waiting for the printouts.)
Yes?
What are you doing, Head Chef?
I'm writing Broccolino Basiliano on the menu.
While you're at it...
We're actually at the photo studio printing out photos.
"We make our own rice cakes."
It'll be really cute...
if you can write a phrase to emphasize that.
Do you want me to write it on my own?
- Yes.
- Write whatever you want.
- Okay.
- Got it.
Thank you.
When are you going to be back?
We're printing out photos, so it'll take...
about 20 to 30 minutes.
We'll be back in 40 minutes.
Please come a little faster.
Yes. I'm sorry, but what is this about?
Just hurry back. I'm anxious.
- Okay.
Okay.
Why is she anxious?
- But when we help her, - It's separation anxiety.
She's not that thrilled about it.
- But why...
- She doesn't like it.
She doesn't like our help, so I wonder why she's anxious.
Young Ji on Space Rice Cake is a different person.
Come on. When there are four people working in a rice cake store,
and two people are gone, won't you be anxious?
Will you be anxious or not?
I'm brutally anxious. I'm Brutally Mars now.
Gosh. I'm totally Brutally Mars now.
(The main reason she is anxious)
Gosh. What kind of nightmares will the basils give me?
For the basil dish, they want a stronger flavour of basil.
I'll try it with the leftover rice cakes.
- I'll make a medium-sized one.
- Okay.
(Adding 1 cup of milk)
(Adding 2 cups of heavy cream)
(The basil pesto is well-aged.)
Do the magic for me, Basil Pesto.
(Adding generous amount of the pesto as requested)
(Giving it a nice stir)
There are rice cakes we won't use.
Please understand...
even though they look ugly.
They're freshly made rice cakes.
(Adding rice cakes in various shapes)
(Tasting the sauce)
It tastes much more like basil.
- I can taste the basil very well.
- Can you?
Yes, I can.
(Adding pepper to implement the second feedback)
This requires lots of work.
It drives me nuts.
It looks tasty, though.
(The basil tteokbokki with lots of intricate details)
After that, I won't add the sun dried tomatoes,
because I don't want to waste them.
(But it's okay to add some crushed peppers.)
(The head chef tries a bite.)
(The sous chef tries it too.)
(How sweet.)
It's tasty, though.
(A repeat customer)
It's really good.
It's so tricky to make,
but it tastes so good.
Honestly, even a shoe would taste good with this sauce.
Yes, that's true.
It's so good.
Okay. The basil one is good to go.
(The simulation was a total success!)
Now, what do we have to do now?
I'm going to make fries for an hour and rice cakes for another hour.
(Covering broccoli in batter)
(But in a modern-dance style)
Two, one.
Broccoli.
(She removes them and drains the oil.)
When many customers come,
I'll serve them the best meal.
(Tater tots)
Aren't these pretty?
(And various seafood fries)
Yes. Nice.
(Pre-frying done to save time)
(Next is jeolpyeon's turn.)
(This is not Episode 2.)
It's a war all day long.
(The jeolpyeon noodles are piling up fast.)
This is only for eight servings.
Broccolino Basiliano.
- You might not know this.
- Yes?
Yesterday...
- You might not know this.
- Yes?
Yesterday at the grocery store and general store,
they spent about 300 dollars.
- To buy beef and all?
- That's right.
That means we have about 100 dollars right now.
(Laughing)
Mimi.
The grocery we shopped and all yesterday and today...
cost about 300 dollars.
What? Then we spent everything we made yesterday.
Tell them to stop buying groceries.
(The service team is back happily without knowing anything.)
- Gosh. What a beautiful day.
- Gosh. It's exhausting.
- We're back.
- Hello.
Welcome back.
- Yes.
- Good job.
This is for you, Young Ji.
- Your arm sleeves. Yes.
- Thank you.
- These are red.
- Those are red.
Red represents tteokbokki.
That's right.
- It's warm. Thank you.
- Yes.
How much did you spend on groceries today?
We need to cut back on our spending.
So I wrote them down...
to cut back on our spending.
- I kept a spending log.
- Okay.
Our goal was to spend under 100 dollars today.
- That's right.
And now...
We spent 26 dollars at the general store.
And we spent 20.4 dollars at the grocery store.
And to buy gimbap,
- we spent 13.50 dollars.
- Gimbap?
- We bought gimbap.
- It's for our lunch.
- Can I tell you one thing?
- Okay.
Didn't you say you'd ask before you buy something?
I thought I didn't need to ask when I was buying lunch.
- Also, we bought...
- Yes.
The photos cost 80 dollars.
- It's a bit small.
- But they look super good.
- This is the vibe.
- They look like this.
Gosh. Thank you.
- Good job.
- It was just a miscommunication.
- We just need to sell more today.
- Yes.
What time is it?
- It's about 11:10am.
- About 11:10am. Okay.
Should we get some snacks right now?
You too, Mimi. Stop working on the jeolpyeon noodles.
It's good.
It's so pretty.
(Enjoying mini gimbap while enjoying the ocean view)
I think chestnut tiramisu will sell well.
I think it'll sell well too.
- It's okay to sell many.
- Okay.
- But the kids don't eat much.
- You're right.
I think it's hard to read.
Only the original tteokbokki is easy to read.
- They're difficult names.
- We can't tell. The sodas too.
For Broccolino Basiliano,
please give a good explanation.
Tell them it's tasty.
(Got it.)
Let the second day begin!
- Let's go!
- Go!
Will you play our show's soundtrack,
"Dream High."
(Playing it with their mouths right away)
Its lyrics talk about us.
(Singing)
(I dream high)
(I dream)
(When life is tough)
(I hold hands)
(Putting on a beaming face)
- Mimi.
- We keep reminding it.
And we pray.
At the height of my fear
(1 minute before it opens)
- Are you ready?
- I'm ready.
- Honesty.
- Humility.
- Ahk.
- I love you.
Don't you love us?
I love you.
- We're now open for business.
- We're open for business.
(Space Rice Cake is open for its 2nd day.)
- Come in.
- Come on.
(Current Time: 12pm)
Let's go.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
Thanks for coming.
Please feel free to look around and take a seat.
(Customers who are friends)
- They've been waiting.
- Okay.
- Hello.
- Hi.
How big is your party?
Thank you.
- Do you want to sit outside?
- The outdoors will be better.
(Thanks to the sunny weather, )
(they've opened the outdoor tables for the first time.)
(It's filed with customers in no time.)
Mimiana.
(The kitchen team in the meantime...)
- Mimiana.
- Yes, Indiana.
We'll make over 500 dollars today, Mimiana.
- We should make more.
- We'll make 1,000 dollars.
- Mimiana.
- Yes.
We have a group coming today.
Since you're our first customers of the day,
do you want me to explain the menus for both of you?
- Yes.
- Good.
This is a dish we're introducing for the first time today.
- Let's do it together.
- Two, three.
- Broccolino Basiliano.
- Broccolino Basiliano, - Yes.
For those who like creamy dishes,
Broccolino Basiliano will be an excellent choice.
- The Jade Emperor.
- Yes.
As for Jade Emperor Tteokbokki...
It's on your left, kid.
When we die, we go to the other side.
Then we'll meet the Jade Emperor.
It's so spicy that it'll kill you.
As for the Jade Emperor Tteokbokki,
since our head chef is Lee Young Ji,
you have to expect a dopamine rush.
Please take a look at the menu and talk about it.
- Thank you.
(We'll excuse ourselves now.)
(Ending in a traditional style)
The ending was great.
(Running away out of embarrassment)
(Meanwhile, the chefs wither away while waiting for the orders.)
(Nervous)
Not yet. I gave a kind explanation of the menus to the customers.
- Thank you.
- Like a fine dining restaurant,
- it was a fine explanation.
- So?
Not yet. Please wait.
- They need time to think.
- I'm sorry.
- They need to decide.
- I thought you'd tell us.
Mom, I want the Jade Emperor Tteokbokki.
No, it'll be too spicy.
First, let's get the pollack roe and clam pasta.
And one original tteokbokki.
Here comes dongchimi.
Do we finally get to use that ladle?
Yes, ladle it at once.
(The new ladle handles dongchimi well.)
This is awesome.
Mimi, these smaller crocodiles are cute, aren't they?
- They're cute.
- They bought them for me.
- That's good.
- Yu Jin and Eun Ji did.
Don't yell at them for spending money, then.
- No.
- They get you good stuff.
I don't yell at them.
(Relieved)
- Mimiana, can I tell you something?
- Okay.
We made 400 dollars yesterday.
They spent 300 dollars on groceries.
- They crossed the line.
- Yes.
(A lame excuse)
That was too much.
(In the meantime, Eun Ji goes to get the first order.)
Yes?
One small Broccolino.
- Okay.
- One tteokramisu chestnut.
Okay.
They will be delicious. Thank you.
Thank you.
- Would you like to order?
- Yes.
Okay.
A pomegranate and a coffee.
(The table with a child customer: Original, tiramisu, slushies)
Okay. We have an order.
(Scurrying over)
Go back to your position.
(Following obediently)
One small original tteokbokki.
One clam pasta.
One small broccoli tteokbokki.
Small broccoli tteokbokki.
One tteokramisu chestnut.
And one small original tteokbokki.
(Orders for Young Ji)
(Small original, small original, and small basil)
(Orders for Mimi: Clam pasta)
Let the spirits possess you.
You are looking great.
(The business spirit sets the broth first.)
I'll serve the original ones first.
- We'll make the original first.
- Okay.
After serving the original ones...
The tteokbokki sauce is perfect today.
Yes. It's crazy.
- It's the best one so far.
- It's really tasty.
(The spirits praise today's sauce.)
(While the broth comes to a boil, )
Excuse me.
(the new menu is about to begin.)
(The heavy cream is soft.)
(And the milk is flavourful.)
I added half a cup of milk.
(You'll be shocked when you try it.)
(The highlight of this tteokbokki is the basil pesto.)
(She boldly adds a big ladleful.)
(The more the tastier.)
Okay.
(Then she stirs it gently.)
(It's perfect light green.)
I love you.
(While the stoves are busy working, )
(Mimi gets the fries ready without any problem.)
Young Ji, add two pieces for the small dish.
Okay.
You can make it while dissolving it, Young Ji.
- You can do it.
- Okay.
(Looking miserable)
(Laughing nervously)
I think it'll work if you add it gently.
It's stiff.
Take your time.
(Failed)
(How could this be?)
(The night before)
- I...
- Measure the length, and...
I think I'll put it in the fridge too.
- Make sure to coil it.
- Okay.
(She decided to keep the leftovers in the fridge to save money.)
Please take them out.
- Do you want me to?
- Yes.
(Back to the present)
Take your time.
(A quick trivia)
(Usually, garaetteok is stored in a dry environment.)
(You can keep it in the fridge...)
(if it'll be consumed in 1 to 2 days.)
(However, )
(the problem here is caused...)
(because she kept it in the fridge without making a coil.)
Five minutes after serving the pasta,
it'll be perfect to serve the original...
Was it the broccoli one? What did they order?
- Where are the scissors?
- Pass me the scissors, Yu Jin.
- Thank you.
- There you go.
(A bit surprised)
Please wait. It needs to simmer for a while.
Gosh. I didn't expect this.
(An unexpected incident occurs every other day.)
(Feeling dejected)
- It's totally fine.
- It needs to be boiled for a while.
I'm sorry.
(It's sad, but she had to do it as a chef.)
Okay. I'll set the timer now.
Okay.
(Hard tteokbokki status)
(10 minutes from now)
(The customers wait without knowing it.)
Why don't we get them their slushies now?
Here are your pomegranate slushy and coffee slushy.
- Thank you.
- Yes, thank you.
Is it okay to add my love to it?
That sounds good.
- It's in it now.
- Thank you.
Will you do it together?
Thank you.
Enjoy your food.
(Serving love to customers)
- I need more time to boil it.
- That's okay.
Sorry about that.
(Firm tteokbokki finally starts boiling.)
(Young Ji's heart is boiling down too.)
(In fact, the basil tteokbokki is boiling weakly.)
(The only thing they can rely on is...)
(Chef Mimi's pollack roe and clam pasta.)
(Plenty of pollack roe)
(Stir-frying with the technique she learned in 2 days)
- Are you okay? Thank you.
- I'm okay.
I was worried about how they were doing.
No wonder it takes a long time because they're making everything.
(It's time.)
(People outside can hear her yelling.)
"It's time."
Can I get two small originals now?
- I need about two minutes.
- Okay.
A small original and clam pasta.
Clam pasta is ready.
(Meanwhile, clam pasta is ready.)
It's coming.
Thank you for waiting.
We appreciate it.
(Pollack roe and clam pasta)
Who's the chef?
Don't be surprised.
It's Chef Kim Mimi.
She's possessed by the rice cake ghost.
She won't listen to anything I say.
Yes?
(Having a slushy due to hunger)
- We're serving in order.
- Okay.
It's only our second day.
(Feeling sorry)
I'm rushing them inside.
- It's okay.
- I'm sorry, young lady.
We'll cheer up.
Why don't you pat my butt to cheer me up?
Cheer up.
Thank you. That was nice.
(Deeply grateful)
(The first customers try the food.)
It tastes like pasta, but very chewy one.
(They seem to like the clam pasta.)
I like it. They're very good.
Small original will be ready in two minutes.
- Okay.
- Keep up the good work.
The toppings will make the small size look better.
I've changed my strategy.
(The sauce has really soaked into the tteokbokki.)
- Two, right?
- Yes.
You can use the ones on the left.
(Place various toppings on the top.)
Original is coming up.
(Small original tteokbokki is ready.)
Small original tteokbokki is here.
Hello. Your tteokbokki is here.
(Trying the tteokbokki she's been waiting)
- Do you like it?
- So good.
This place makes good rice cake. The rice cake is tasty.
- Try it.
- It's very chewy.
It's perfect. You're doing great.
- Keep up the good pace.
- How's their reaction?
- They're going crazy.
- Are they? That's good.
- They love it.
- That's good.
Let's record their reaction and play it for Young Ji tonight.
I appreciate it.
(The current status on firm tteokbokki)
(What about me?)
(Basil tteokbokki is left alone.)
So...
(It's served with a little special fritters.)
- Right? It's hot.
- It's very hot.
I can't miss out on the presentation. Thank you.
You got it.
Black pepper.
On the right too. Good.
You can go wider. To the side.
- Good. To the left.
- Left?
That's good.
(All completed)
(Serving right away)
Your pollack...
Broccolino Basiliano...
is here. It's hot.
It's hot.
(Small Broccolino Basiliano)
(Taking a picture first)
(How does the first Broccolino Basiliano taste?)
It's good.
It tastes like a real Italian dish.
It goes well with the spicy dish.
(Peace arrives in Italy... No, Space Rice Cake.)
(The chef is finally smiling again.)
Turn around.
(Beyond Mimi who's washing the dishes, )
(the customers start to appear.)
They're approaching like Prince Su Yang.
You mean customers?
(Prince Su Yang want to place an order.)
- We have an order.
- Okay.
- It's ready.
- Wait. Give me 20 seconds.
I'm serving water to the new table.
I'll serve dongchimi.
(Epilogue)
She's a princess.
- I have the mouth of horror.
- She...
- She's Jin Princess.
- I'm Jin Princess.
- The mouth of truth and horror.
- Right.
- She's our princess.
- I'm the mouth of horror.
Right. Our princess...
No, I'm Pearl since I'm the mouth of truth...
With Jin Princess...
(Next episode)
(Space Rice Cake releases a new menu.)
(I've been to Bangkok before.)
(When I heard we were opening a rice cake, this came to my mind.)
(I tried this in Bangkok.)
(You're the master of desserts.)
(Developed by the master of desserts)
(The dessert that will open your eyes wide)
(Wait. We have to sell this.)
(People of all ages like it.)
(We're off to a very good start.)
(Starting the dinner business with comfort)
(Or so they thought...)
They're swarming in.
(The biggest group of customers enters.)
(The enthusiastic lecture...)
(raises the demand.)
(One medium ghost pepper tteokbokki)
(One small ghost pepper tteokbokki)
(The head chef experiences a crisis.)
(They barely overcome the first crisis.)
(The backlog creates confusion.)
(They end up overloaded.)
(Trying to stop the orders)
(Failed)
(The wait is...)
(In denial)
(Chaos from the kitchen to the hall)
(I'm really sorry.)
(The Earth Arcaders are experiencing chaos.)
(But there's nothing we can't do.)
(We grow!)
(The Earth Arcaders' next step is the glutinous rice cake.)
That looks good.
(That's cute.)
(You can see how chewy it is in a glance.)
(Potato cream tteoksagna)
(Black sesame Torong ice cream)
(The cheese makes it even chewier.)
(And the dessert that looks good and tastes good)
(Exclaiming)
(Look forward to the ever-changing rice cake!)
(Space Rice Cake)